压制:随Feng
One More Night
一夜停留
Maroon 5
歌手:魔力红乐队
You and I go hard
我们的关系不断僵化
at each other like we going to war
在彼此看来都是紧张到一触即发
You and I go rough
生活变得艰难
we keep throwing things and slamming the doors
我们唯一的交流变成了摔打东西和大力关门彼此隔绝
You and I get sore
我们变得易怒、歇斯底里
then dysfunctional we stuck keeping score
以互踩痛处而相互较量
You and I get sick
我们的所作所为越来越超出常规
they all know that we can't do this no more
连旁人都看不下去了
But baby there you again
但亲爱的你再一次
there you again making me love you
再一次让我爱上了你
Yeah I stopped using my head
是的 我已经停止了思考
using my head let it all go
思考怎么放手
Got you stuck on my body
你紧紧的贴着我的身体
on my body like a tattoo
就像枚带有疼痛的印记
And now i'm feeling stupid
现在我感觉到自己的愚蠢
feeling stupid crawling back to you
愚蠢又悄悄溜回你身边
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die
所以我以生命起誓
that i'll only stay with you one more night
我只会和你再待最后一晚
And I know i've said it a million times
我知道我已经说过千万遍
But i'll only stay with you one more night
但这真的是我们相处的最后一夜
Trying to tell you no
我试图拒绝你
but my body keeps on telling you yes
可我的身体却自行接受
Trying to tell you stop
我试图停下
but your lipstick got me so out of breath
但你口红的颜色都快夺走了我的呼吸
I'd be waking up in the morning probably hating myself
我总在清晨醒来时无比厌恶这样的自己
And i'd be waking up feeling sastified but guilty as hell
我在醒来时候 心中满是满足和如临地狱的罪恶感
But baby there you again there you again making me love you
但亲爱的 你又再一次让我爱上你了
Yeah I stopped using my head using my head let it all go
是的 我已经放弃了思考权衡 我不会再放手
Got you stuck on my body on my body like a tattoo
让你紧紧缠绕我的身体 就像枚带有疼痛的印记
And now i'm feeling stupid feeling stupid crawling back to you
我现在真的后悔悄悄地溜回你的身旁
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die
所以我以死起誓
that i'll only stay with you one more night
只再和你共度最后一晚
And I know i've said it a million times
我知道我已经说了千万遍
But i'll only stay with you one more night
到这真的是最后一晚
Yeah baby give me one more night
亲爱的再让我和你多待一夜
再给我一夜回忆
Yeah baby give me one more night
最后一夜
But baby there you again there you again making me love you
但亲爱的你又让我再次爱上你
Yeah I stopped using my head using my head let it all go
我已经不能再维持理性，不能再对你放手
Got you stuck on my body on my body like a tattoo
想让你始终待在我的身旁，像枚滴血的刺青
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
So I cross my heart and I hope to die
我以我的生命发誓
that i'll only stay with you one more night
这会是你我共处的最后一夜
And I know i've said it a million times
我知道这句话我已说了千万遍
But i'll only stay with you one more night
但我只会再和你多待这最后一夜
(yeah baby give me one more night)
(但我只会再和你多待这最后一夜)
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die
所以我用我的生命发誓
that i'll only stay with you one more night
这真的会是最后一晚
压制:随Feng
And I know i've said it a million times
我知道这话我已经说过千万遍
But i'll only stay with you one more night
但我此刻只想与你共度今夜时光